{
    "stTableCheckBoxInit": "body > div:nth-child(8) > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(6) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(4) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div > table > tbody > tr:nth-child(1) > td.GKCQ-U1BHM.GKCQ-U1BEO.GKCQ-U1BBP > div > span > img",
    "stTableCheckBoxRowEvenBack": ") > td.GKCQ-U1BGM.GKCQ-U1BEO > div > span > img",
    "stTableCheckBoxRowEvenFront": "body > div:nth-child(8) > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(6) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(4) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div > table > tbody > tr:nth-child(",
    "stTableCheckBoxRowOddBack": ") > td.GKCQ-U1BHM.GKCQ-U1BEO > div > span > img",
    "stTableCheckBoxRowOddFront": "body > div:nth-child(8) > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(6) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(4) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div > table > tbody > tr:nth-child(",
    "stTableContainerBackInfo": ") > td:nth-child(5) > div > table > tbody > tr > td.GKCQ-U1BICE > span",
    "stTableContainerBackType": ") > td:nth-child(5) > div > table > tbody > tr > td.GKCQ-U1BHCE",
    "stTableContainerFront": "body > div:nth-child(8) > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(6) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(4) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div > table > tbody > tr:nth-child(",
    "stTableContainerInit": "body > div:nth-child(8) > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(6) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(4) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div > table > tbody > tr:nth-child(1) > td:nth-child(5) > div > table > tbody > tr > td.GKCQ-U1BICE",
    "stTableDescriptionBack": ") > td:nth-child(3) > div",
    "stTableDescriptionFront": "body > div:nth-child(8) > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(6) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(4) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div > table > tbody > tr:nth-child(",
    "stTableLocationBackInfo": ") > td:nth-child(6) > div > table > tbody > tr > td.GKCQ-U1BICE > span",
    "stTableLocationBackLocType": ") > td:nth-child(6) > div > table > tbody > tr > td.GKCQ-U1BHCE",
    "stTableLocationFront": "body > div:nth-child(8) > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(6) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(4) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div > table > tbody > tr:nth-child(",
    "stTableLotSerialBack": ") > td:nth-child(4) > div",
    "stTableLotSerialFront": "body > div:nth-child(8) > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(6) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(4) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div > table > tbody > tr:nth-child(",
    "stTableProductBack": ") > td:nth-child(2) > span",
    "stTableProductFront": "body > div:nth-child(8) > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(6) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(4) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div > table > tbody > tr:nth-child(",
    "stTableQAVBack": ") > td:nth-child(8) > div",
    "stTableQAVFront": "body > div:nth-child(8) > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(6) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(4) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div > table > tbody > tr:nth-child(",
    "stTableQOHBack": ") > td:nth-child(7) > div",
    "stTableQOHFront": "body > div:nth-child(8) > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(6) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(4) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div > table > tbody > tr:nth-child(",
    "stTableQRBack": ") > td:nth-child(9) > div",
    "stTableQRFront": "body > div:nth-child(8) > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(6) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(4) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div > table > tbody > tr:nth-child(",
    "stTableZSMSHoldBackEven": ") > td.GKCQ-U1BGM GKCQ-U1BNO > div",
    "stTableZSMSHoldBackOdd": ") > td.GKCQ-U1BHM GKCQ-U1BNO > div",
    "stTableZSMSHoldFront": "body > div:nth-child(8) > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(6) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(4) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div > table > tbody > tr:nth-child(",
    "stTableZSMSHoldInit": "body > div:nth-child(8) > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(6) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(4) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div > table > tbody > tr:nth-child(1) > td.GKCQ-U1BHM.GKCQ-U1BBP.GKCQ-U1BNO > div",
    "stTableRowFront": "body > div:nth-child(8) > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(6) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(4) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div > table > tbody > tr:nth-child(",
    "stTableRowBack": ")",
    "stTableNextPage": "body > div:nth-child(8) > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(6) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(4) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > table > tbody > tr > td:nth-child(1) > div > table > tbody > tr > td > table > tbody > tr > td.GKCQ-U1BEDE > img",
    "stTablePreviousPage":"body > div:nth-child(8) > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(6) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(4) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > table > tbody > tr > td:nth-child(1) > div > table > tbody > tr > td > table > tbody > tr > td.GKCQ-U1BBDE > img",
    "stAutoSourceInvalidKits": "body > div:nth-child(8) > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(6) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > table > tbody > tr > td:nth-child(3) > table > tbody > tr > td > span",
    "stAutoSourceInvalidKitsErrorPrompt": "body > div.gwt-PopupPanel > div > div > table > tbody > tr > td > div > div",
    "stTableSelectAll": "body > div:nth-child(8) > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(6) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(4) > div > div:nth-child(3) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div:nth-child(2) > div > div > div > table > tbody > tr > td.GKCQ-U1BAO.GKCQ-U1BEO > div > span > img"
}